Guide to the Cornell Migrant Program campus collection,1953-2006.
Cornell Migrant Program campus collection,1953-2006.
- Series VIII. Migrant Education Studies
  - Migrant Children: Education and HHS Need to Improve the Exchange of Participant Information, 1999 (Box 42, Folder 54)
- Series IX. Diversity
  - Racism, 1984-1990 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Wayne Action for Racial Equality - Tax Exemption, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Wayne Action for Racial Equality (W.A.R.E.), 1988-2001 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Multicultural Education Resource (W.A.R.E.) N ew York StatePart 1, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Multicultural Education Resource (W.A.R.E.) New York State Part 2, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - Institutional Racism Conference, 1988-01-27 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Racism - Social Trends and Outlook Conference, 1988 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Black Focus (newsletter), 1989 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Institutional Racism Conference - Letter from Hart and Lewis to Dean Call and Com. McGuire, 1989 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Cornell Anti-Discrimination Project (New York State Dept. Social Services) - Kay Embrey, 1991-1993 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Anti-Discrimination Training Program (Farmworker Legal Services) - Kay Embrey, 1992-1994 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Cultural Diversity In-service Advisory Group, 1991-1993 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Managing Diversity Within Cooperative Extension, 1992 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Diversity Within Cornell Cooperative Extension, 1993-2000 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Racial Harmony and Diversity Program (Chemical Bank) - Kathy Castania, 1993 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Anti-Racism Workshop - WARE and NAACP, 1993-05-08 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - Wayne County Intercultural Program, 1994 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Cultural Diversity Project (within Cornell Migrant Program), 1994-2004 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - Cornell Migrant Program Diversity Project Reports (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Cultural Diversity - A Rural Response (USDA) - Kay Embrey/Kathy Castania, 1997-1998 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Impact of Immigration on Rural Communities (USDA) - Kay Embrey (not funded), 1988 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Resolving Rural Racial Conflicts (USDA) - Kathy Castania, 1999-2001 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Change Agent States for Diversity - Kathy Castania, 2001-2002 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Building Inclusive Rural Communities (USDA) - Betty Garcia Mathewson, 2001-2004 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - Intercultural Harmony (Laura Jane Musser Fund) - Betty Garcia Mathewson, 2002-2003 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Change Agent States for Diversity - Promising Practices, 2003 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Human Ecology - Diversity (Allan Johnson visit), 2003 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Diversity "Entrepreneurial" Account, 2001-2004 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Diversity Program Expansion Request to Dean Patsy Brannon, 2004 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Working Together / Anti-Racism / Opening Doors, 1988-2003 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Working Together to Eliminate Racism (New York State Workshop), 1992 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  - Working Together / Anti-Racism / Opening Doors, 1994-1999 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Working Together to Eliminate Racism, 1992-09-16 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Opening Doors, 1993-05-20 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Walking Through Prejudices - Migrant Parents (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Opening Doors - Science Teachers (Box 19, Folder 7)
  - Opening Doors, 1993-06-04 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - Working Together to Eliminate Racism, 1993-11-08 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Opening Doors, 1994-08-30 (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Opening Doors, 1994-11-08 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Opening Doors, 1994-10-26 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - Opening Doors, 1995-01-11 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Opening Doors, 1995-04-10 (Box 19, Folder 14)
  - Opening Doors, 1995-05-17 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Opening Doors, 1995-07-12 (Box 19, Folder 16)
  - Opening Doors, 1995-06-14 (Box 19, Folder 17)
  - Opening Doors, 1995-07-19 (Box 19, Folder 18)
  - Opening Doors, 1995-09-20 (Box 19, Folder 19)
  - Opening Doors, 1995-09-29 (Box 19, Folder 20)
  - Opening Doors, 1995-10-18 (Box 19, Folder 21)
  - Opening Doors, 1995-11-10 (Box 19, Folder 22)
  - Sodus Central School, 1995-11-15 (Box 19, Folder 23)
  - Opening Doors, 1995-01-10 (Box 19, Folder 24)
  - Opening Doors, 1996-02-28 (Box 19, Folder 25)
  - Opening Doors, 1996-03-13 (Box 19, Folder 26)
  - Opening Doors, 1996-04-16 (Box 19, Folder 27)
  - Opening Doors, 1996-05-29 (Box 19, Folder 28)
  - Opening Doors, 1996-10-09 (Box 19, Folder 29)
  - Creating Partnerships - Management for the Future, 1996-12-03 (Box 19, Folder 30)
  - Opening Doors, 1997-01-15 (Box 19, Folder 31)
  - Opening Doors, 1997-02-05 (Box 19, Folder 32)
  - Opening Doors, 1997-04-02 (Box 19, Folder 33)
  - Opening Doors, 1997-06-11 (Box 19, Folder 34)
  - Opening Doors, 1997-07-18 (Box 19, Folder 35)
  - Opening Doors, 1998-01-21 (Box 19, Folder 36)
  - Opening Doors, 1998-03-04 (Box 19, Folder 37)
  - Opening Doors, 1998-04-22 (Box 19, Folder 38)
  - Opening Doors, 1998-05-06 (Box 19, Folder 39)
  - Opening Doors, 1998-06-30 (Box 19, Folder 40)
  - Opening Doors, 1998-08-05 (Box 19, Folder 41)
  - Opening Doors, 1998-09-23 (Box 19, Folder 42)
  - Opening Doors, 1999-01-13 (Box 19, Folder 43)
  - Opening Doors, 1999-03-10 (Box 19, Folder 44)
  - Opening Doors, 1999-04-14 (Box 19, Folder 45)
  - Opening Doors, 1999-07-26 (Box 19, Folder 46)
  - Opening Doors, 1999-08-17 (Box 19, Folder 47)
  - Opening Doors, 1999-10-06 (Box 19, Folder 48)
  - Opening Doors, 2000-01-12 (Box 19, Folder 49)
  - Opening Doors, 2000-03-22 (Box 19, Folder 50)
  - Opening Doors, 2000-04-11 (Box 19, Folder 51)
  - Opening Doors, 2000-08-15 (Box 19, Folder 52)
  - Opening Doors, 2000-10-18 (Box 19, Folder 53)
  - Learning is Magical, 2000-11-01 (Box 19, Folder 54)
  - Opening Doors, 2000-12-12 (Box 19, Folder 55)
  - Opening Doors, 2001-03-28 (Box 19, Folder 56)
  - Opening Doors, 2001-06-26 (Box 19, Folder 57)
  - Opening Doors, 2003-08-20 (Box 19, Folder 58)
  - Diversity Release Form - School of Social Work - Texas, 1986 (Box 19, Folder 59)
  - Building Bridges Conference - Workshop Presentation "Unlearning Racism" - June 9-10,1988, 1988 (Box 19, Folder 60)
  - Diversity Workshop for So. Cayuga County Coalition for Diversity and Tolerance - King Ferry, 1994-09-13 (Box 19, Folder 61)
  - Diversity Workshop - Wayne Fingerlakes BOCES Teacher Center, 1994-03-18 (Box 19, Folder 62)
  - Cornell Fact Sheet - The Evolving Language of Diversity (Box 19, Folder 63)
  - Oswego College - Community Coalition (Box 19, Folder 64)
  - Cornell Fact Sheet - "What is Diversity" (Box 19, Folder 65)
  - ROI Action Pledge Task Force (Box 19, Folder 66)
  - ROI Organizational Change Initiative with Cornell Migrant Program, 2002 (Box 19, Folder 67)
  - Subseries IXa. Kathy Fox Castania
    - New York State Migrant Education (Kathy Fox/Castania), 1982-1992 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - New York State Migrant Education (Kathy Fox/Castania), 1993-1994 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Wayne County Minority (Multicultural) Arts - Correspondence, 1984-1997 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Wayne County Minority (Multicultural) Arts Programs, 1984-1990 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Wayne County Minority (Multicultural) Arts Programs, 1991-2004 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Wayne County Multicultural Arts - Finance, 1991-1998 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Wayne County Minority (Multicultural) Arts, 1985-1992 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Wayne Co. Minority Arts Project, Inc. - Overview and Minutes, 1993-1998 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Wayne County Multicultural Arts - Mexican Fiesta, 1993-2003 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Wayne County Minority (Multicultural) Arts - Job Descriptions (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Women's Writing Workshop, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Wayne County Multicultural Arts Audio Tapes (Box 20)
    - Wayne County Multicultural Arts - Photos and Slides (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - WCMAP Negatives (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Haitian Night Photos, 1984 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - WCMAP - Assorted Photos (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - Mexican Fiesta Photos, 1993 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Mexican Fiesta Photos, 1999 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Mexican Fiesta Photos, 2000 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Mexican Fiesta, 2002 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Mexican Fiesta - Miscellaneous (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Sonia Sanchez (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Hispanic Dance Group - Shoot by Cornell, 1992 (Box 20, Folder 22)
- Series X. Nutrition and Health
  - Subseries Xa. Nutrition
    - Interstate Migrant Nutrition (New York and Florida), 1972 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Interstate Migrant Nutrition (New York and Florida), 1973 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Interstate Migrant Nutrition (New York and Florida), 1974 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Interstate Migrant Nutrition, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Interstate Migrant Nutrition (New York and Florida), 1976 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Interstate Migrant Nutrition (New York and Florida), 1977 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Interstate Migrant Nutrition (New York and Florida), 1978-1990 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Subcontract with University of Florida - Migrant Nutrition, 1986 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Nutrition Research - King Ferry, New York (1965) and Palm Beach, Florida (1961), 1961, 1965 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Nutrition Education Proposals - New York State Education Department, 1973-1975 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Migrant Nutrition Education - Proposals/Evaluations, 1973-1975 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Nutrition Education Funding, 1974-1978 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Interstate Migrant Nutrition - Program Funding Inc. (PFI), 1975-1976 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Migrant Nutrition, 1975-1977 (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Wayne County Migrant Nutrition Education - Partricia Grace, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Health and Nutrition - Suffolk County, New York, 1976-1977 (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - BOCES Migrant Nutrition (proposal) Suffolk County, 1976-1977 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Nutrition Education/Chautauqua CCE - Steve Johnson, 1976-1977 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - Nutrition Education Film - "Pick and Choose", 1976-1978 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Migrant Education Advisory Committee - Steve Johnson, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - EFNEP Funds for Migrant Nutrition, 1977 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - New York State W.I.C. Association, 1979-1980 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Migrant Health and Nutrition Education - Wayne and Chautauqua, 1979-1982 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - "The Special Supplemental Food Program for Women, Infants and Children (WIC) - How Can It Work Better?" - Comptroller General of the U.S., 1979 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Food Policy White Paper (New York State), 1981 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Migrant Workers - Assessment of Nutritional Status, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Providing Services to Migrant Farmworkers (WIC-USDA), 1986 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Migrant Nutrition Program (New York and Florida), 1988 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Termination of Migrant Education Program (New York and Florida), 1989 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Pick and Choose (Migrant Nutrition Education), 1991 (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - The Nutritional Status of Migrant Children...in New York State, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Farmworker Nutrition Education Resource Guide (USDOH HS), 1993 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Subseries Xb. Health
    - Mobile Health Clinic, 1971,1981 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - Oral Health for Migrant Families - Project REACH, 1973-1975 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - Rushville Clinic (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - Rushville Health Center - Steve Johnson, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - Kim Van Atta Resignation - Rushville Health Center, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - Lakes Area Regional Medical Program (Buffalo), 1973-1974 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - Oral Health Education - Orange County, 1973-1980 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - Lakes Area Regional Medical Program, 1974-1975 (Box 22, Folder 8)
    - Hypertension Screening - Steve Johnson, 1974-1976 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - Orange County Migrant Health (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - Pine Island Health Clinic - Steve Johnson, 1976 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - Emergency Medical/Dental - New York State Ag. And Markets / Beverly A. (Norton) Bove, 1976-1977 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - Health Care - Ag. and Markets and Migrant Education, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 13)
    - Western New York Grants Administration Services, Inc., 1977 (Box 22, Folder 14)
    - Comprehensive Health - Orange County, 1977 (Box 22, Folder 15)
    - Comprehensive Migrant Health Education - Suffolk County (New York State), 1978-79 (Box 22, Folder 16)
    - Health Committee - Cornell Cooperative Extension, 1979-1982 (Box 22, Folder 17)
    - Migrant Health, 1980-1990 (Box 22, Folder 18)
    - East Coast Entitlement Project (Health), 1981-1983 (Box 22, Folder 19)
    - Correspondence - Frank Barry, Child Abuse and Neglect, 1979 (Box 22, Folder 20)
    - Interstate Child Abuse and Neglect Project, 1980 (Box 22, Folder 21)
    - Preventing Child Abuse in the Harvest: A Handbook for Migrant Educators, 1985 (Box 22, Folder 22)
    - Child Abuse and Neglect Among Mexican American Migrants, 1981 (Box 22, Folder 23)
    - A Study of Attitudes Toward Child Abuse and Child Rearing Among Mexican American Migrants in Texas, 1982 (Box 22, Folder 24)
    - Child Abuse and Neglect in the Eastern Migratory Stream, 1983 (Box 22, Folder 25)
    - Migrant Child Abuse and Neglect Articles - Larson, Doris, Alvarez, 1987-1989 (Box 22, Folder 26)
    - Child Abuse and Neglect (Box 22, Folder 27)
    - Helping Migrant Farmworkers Obtain Medicaid (Video), 1982 (Box 22, Folder 28)
    - Happier (Health Awareness) Project Evaluation, 1984 (Box 22, Folder 29)
    - Maternal and Child Health Services...in Niagara Co. (New York State), 1985 (Box 22, Folder 30)
    - Migrant Health (New York State), 1986 (Box 22, Folder 31)
    - Suffolk County (New York State) Migrant Health Program, 1986 (Box 22, Folder 32)
    - New York State Health Care Campaign - Testimonies, 1987 (Box 22, Folder 33)
    - Interagency Workgroup for Migrant Health Care (New York State), 1987 (Box 22, Folder 34)
    - Mid-Hudson Family Health Services Institute (Box 22, Folder 35)
    - Lockport Clinics (Health and Dental) New York State Dept. Health - Proposals and Reports, 1979-1988 (Box 22, Folder 36)
    - Lockport Dental Clinic (Box 22, Folder 37)
    - Lockport Medical Clinic - Barbara Meeks (Box 22, Folder 38)
    - Founders Clinic - Niagara Co., New York, 1997-2001 (Box 22, Folder 39)
    - Lockport Clinics, 1982-1989 (Box 22, Folder 40)
    - Lockport Clinics - Kathy Fox (Castania), 1983-1984 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Lockport Clinics Training - Kay Embrey, 1986 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Child Health Voucher, 1985-2004 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Child Health Voucher Data, 1991-2004 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Field Sanitation Standards, 1985 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Milbank Memorial Fund (Rural Opportunities, Inc.), 1987 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Occupational Health (New York State), 1988 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Migrant Farmworker Substance Abuse Proposal (Kathy Fox/Castania), 1988 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Health Miscellaneous, 1988-2001 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - AIDS, 1989-1991 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Teach Our Children Well - An AIDS Primer for Migrant Education, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Herb Engman Appointment to New York State Rural Health Council, 1988 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Rural Health Council (New York State), 1988 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Rural Health Council (New York State), 1989 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Rural Health Council (New York State), 1990-1992 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Rural Health Council, 1993-1994 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Atlas of State Profiles...Migrant and Season Farmworkers (U.S. HHS), 1990 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Proposal for the Finger Lakes Migrant Health Coordination Project, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Finger Lakes Migrant Health Care Coordination Project - Mission/Bylaws (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Finger Lakes Migrant Health Care Coordination Project, 1989-1990 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Finger Lakes Migrant Health Care Coordination Project, 1991-1992 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Finger Lakes Migrant Health Care Coordination Project Report, 1992 (Box 23, Folder 22)
    - Finger Lakes Migrant Health Care Coordination Project, 1993-1994 (Box 23, Folder 23)
    - Finger Lakes Migrant Health Care Coordination Project, 1995-1998 (Box 23, Folder 24)
    - Finger Lakes Migrant Health Care Coordination Project, 1990 (Box 23, Folder 25)
    - Rural Health Coalition (New York State), 1990-1993 (Box 23, Folder 26)
    - Migrant Health Center - Newfane (New York), 1992 (Box 23, Folder 27)
    - Office of Minority Health (proposed), 1992 (Box 23, Folder 28)
    - Farmworker Alcohol and Substance Abuse Project (U.S. Rural Health Policy) - Kay Embrey, 1993-1994 (Box 23, Folder 29)
    - Farmworker Alcohol and Substance Abuse Project (U.S. Rural Health Policy) - Kay Embrey, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 30)
    - Farmworker Alcohol and Substance Abuse Project (U.S. Rural Health Policy) - Kay Embrey, 1996-1997 (Box 23, Folder 31)
    - New York Center for Agricultural Medicine and Health, 1994-1997 (Box 23, Folder 32)
    - Cornell/Finger Lakes Migrant Health Program - Eloy Rodriguez, 1997 (Box 23, Folder 33)
    - Oak Orchard Community Health Center, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 34)
    - Environmental Health Priorities Workshop (New York State Department of Health), 1998 (Box 23, Folder 35)
    - Cornell Migrant Health Project (New York State Department of Health) - not funded, 2001 (Box 23, Folder 36)
    - East Coast Migrant Health Stream Forum, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 37)
    - 2002-2003 Migrant Farmworker (Health) Stream Forums, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 38)
    - Migrant and Seasonal Farmworker Access to Health Care, 2003 (Box 23, Folder 39)
  - Subseries Xc. Health Reports
    - Migrant Health Newsline, 1996-2000 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Migrant Health Newsline, 2001-2005 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Migrant Health Clinical Supplement/Streamline, 1984-1996 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Migrant Streamline, 1997-2006 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - UC Agricultural Health and Safety Center at Davis, 1992-1998 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - UC Agricultural Health and Safety Center at Davis, 1999-2006 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - National Children's Center for Rural and Agricultural Health and Safety, 1998-2002 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Migrant and Seasonal Farmworkers - President's Commission on Mental Health, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Food Stamp Participation of Hired Farmworker Families (USDA), 1978 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Medical Utilization Patterns of Hispanic Migrant Farmworkers (Wisconsin), 1981 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Health for the Nation's Harvesters (Helen L. Johnston, 1985 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - The Occupational Health of Migrant and Seasonal Farmworkers in the United States, 1986 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Agriculture at Risk: Ag. Occupational and Environmental Health, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Health Care, Access and Equality - Community and Migrant Health Centers, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Profile of a Population with Complex Health Problems, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Environmental Risks to the Infants and Toddlers of Migrant Farmworkers, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Medicaid Interstate Compacts, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Barriers to Health Care...of Migrant Farmworkers (PA), 1992 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Hired Farmworkers: Health and Well-Being at Risk (GAO), 1992 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Health Problems Among Migrant Farmworkers' Children in the U.S., 1993 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Farmworkers and HIV (National Council of La Raza), 1993 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - HIV/AIDS: A Growing Crisis Among Migrant and Seasonal Farmworkers, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Health Care...For Mixtec Migrant...Families in Madera, Ca, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Cultivating Health: An Agenda for Adolescent Farmworkers, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Losing Ground - The Condition of Farmworkers in America, 1995 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Children and Agriculture: Opportunities for Safety and Health, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Migrant Children's Health Article, 1997-2002 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - When a Farmworker Has a Disability - A Guide for Providers, 1997 (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Suffering in Silence: California's Agricultural Workers, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Fingers to the Bone - U.S. Failure to Protect Child Farmworkers, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Guidelines for the Care of Migrant Farmworkers' Children, 2000 (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Injuries Among Farmworkers in the U.S. (DHHS), 1995, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - Simple Solutions: Ergonomics for Farm Workers (DHHS), 2001 (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - Migrant and Seasonal Hired Adolescent Farmworkers, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - Child Labor - Farmworker Justice Fund, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - Injuries Among Youth on Farms in the U.S. (DHHS), 1998, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 36)
    - Fatal Unintentional Farm Injuries Among Persons Less Than Twenty Years of Age in the United States, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 37)
    - Farmworker Health Outreach Needs Assessment Report, 2001 (Box 24, Folder 38)
    - Protecting the Health and Safety of Migrant and Seasonal Farmworkers in the Northeast, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 39)
    - Childhood Agricultural Injury Prevention, 2002 (Box 24, Folder 40)
    - Reducing Racial and Ethnic Health Disparities, 2003 (Box 24, Folder 41)
    - Migrant and Seasonal Farmworkers: Health Insurance Coverage and Access to Care, 2005 (Box 24, Folder 42)
- Series XI. Pesticides
  - Pesticides Newsletters Examples (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Pesticide Safety for Farm Employees - James Dewey, 1972 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Pesticide Accident Surveillance System - James Dewey, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Pesticide Applicator Core Training Manual - James Dewey, 1975 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Pesticide and Household Poison Safety (Recording), 1979 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - The Pesticide Syndrome: Economic Poisons, Power and Productivity in Agriculture, 1979 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Pesticides - Miscellaneous, 1980-2001 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Pesticides, Health and the Law (Rural America), 1980 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Potential Pesticide Exposure of Migrant Farmworkers (New York State), 1980 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Pesticide Use and Misuse - Rural America, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - Danger in the Field: The Myth of Pesticide Safety, 1980 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - Stronger Enforcement Needed Against Misuse of Pesticides (GAO), 1981 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Potential Pesticide Exposure of Migrant Farmworkers (Morse, et. al.), 1980 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - National Coalition Against the Misuse of Pesticides, 1981-1984 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Pesticides and the Farmworker (AFOP), 1981 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Pesticide Safety for Non-Certifies Mixers, Loaders and Applicators (EPA), 1986 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Farm Guide to the Right to Know Law (Embrey, et. al.), 1987 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - New Directions in Pesticide Use, 1991 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - Pesticide Poisoning Registry (New York State), 1991-1994 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - Pesticides on Farms - Limited Capability Exists to Monitor Occupational Illness and Injuries (GAO), 1993 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - Washed, Peeled, Contaminated - Environmental Working Group, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - Pesticides and Clothing, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - Focus on Pesticides (example), 1998 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - Pesticide Data Program, 1999 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - Always Wear the Right Clothes - Pesticide Protection - Charlotte Coffman, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - Pesticide-Poison Education (New York State) - Dan LaFica, 1975-1977 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - Pesticide Safety Education - Slides, 1975-1979 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - Pesticide and Household Poison Safety Education - Slides and Audio Tapes (Box 26, Folder 28)
  - Pesticide and Household Poison Safety Education, 1975-1979 (Box 26, Folder 29)
  - Pesticide Education Packet - Development of Cornell Migrant Program, 1983 (Box 26, Folder 30)